devero.com 2017-06-08

# DeVero privacy policy

DeVero, Inc cares how information about you is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. The below information describes our privacy policy. By visiting the DeVero, Inc Web site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

The information we learn from clients helps us continually improve DeVero, Inc’ ability to provide you with the products you need. Here are the types of information we gather:

* Information You Give Us: As a result of contacting us or ordering, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; institutions and individuals to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; and financial information pertaining to your orders. We also receive and store any information you enter on our Web site. DeVero, Inc does not trade, sell or otherwise share this information with any other businesses or third parties.

******We share customer information only as described below:**

Protection of DeVero, Inc and others: We will release account and other personal information when it is required to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of DeVero, Inc or others. This does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from clients for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

* Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses DeVero, Inc. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, and through, our Web site.

* Information from Other Sources: We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our mailing lists. This information contains no private information other than e-mail and physical mailing addresses. DeVero, Inc does not engage in consumer profiling nor do we purchase information from any source containing such data.

*What do I do if I do not want DeVero, Inc to collect information with cookies?

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

The Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its web site.

**Communication from DeVero**  
* E-mail Communications: To help us make keep you informed of new products, industry news and events we occasionally send e-mail notifications to our clients. Should you not want to receive such communication from us, simply use the “unsubscribe” link in the email or notify us at info@devero.com.

**Updating this statement**  
DeVero, Inc may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**  
This website contains links to other websites.

DeVero, Inc is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or DeVero, Inc’s treatment of your personal information, please write:

by email to info@devero.com; or  
by post to 300 Park Avenue, San Jose, CA 95110
